bigfitness.com 2008-06-09

# BigFitness.com Privacy Policy

Privacy Statement for www.bigfitness.com

Big Fitness has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: www.bigfitness.com.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart.

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart.

This site contains links to other sites. www.bigfitness.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address) and financial information (like their account or credit card numbers). Contact information from the order form is used to send orders to our customers. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.

Big Fitness uses pixels, or transparent GIF files, to help manage online advertising. These GIF files are provided by our ad management partner, DoubleClick. These files enable DoubleClick to recognize a unique cookie on your Web browser, which in turn enables us to learn which advertisements bring users to our website. The cookie was placed by us, or by another advertiser who works with DoubleClick. With both cookies and Spotlight technology, the information that we collect and share is anonymous and not personally identifiable. It does not contain your name, address, telephone number, or email address. For more information about DoubleClick, including information about how to opt out of these technologies, go to [http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy].

**Public Forums**  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

**Promotional Emails**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional email communications from us. If you no longer wish to receive these emails, please enter your email address below:   

**Correct/Update**  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided. Call the following telephone number: 1-888-292-1807 or email [customerservice@bigfitness.com](mailto:customerservice@bigfitness.com)

**Contacting the Web Site**  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

Big Fitness  
560 Mineral Spring Ave  
webmaster@bigfitness.com
